# Ronil M. Cajan

# PHP Developer

#### Work Experience



Secondary School Teacher Department of Education - Sinonoc National High School

Sept 2021 to Present

- Teach Grade 7 Grade 10 for TLE-ICT
- School ICT Coordinator



Web Developer
Digs Design, Inc
Aug 2020 to May 2021 (9 months)

- Collaborating with development team for solving web development challenges
- Self-directed research and development into implementation of custom plugin and theme coding.
- Consistent and reliable communication with team and project managers for providing time estimates, project archetyping, and project scoping.



Digital Marketer Intern Syntactics, Inc May 2019 to July 2019 (3 months)

• Convey the right business message and reach target audience with personalized marketing strategies by the digital marketing team.

#### **Profile**

I'm a web application developer from the Philippines with experience in creating, debugging and editing web applications(mostly PHP application). Currently, working as a public Teacher and assigned as School ICT. I enjoy creating application that solved business problems and contributing my skills to the organization where I worked.

#### Contact Info

#### Click <u>here</u> for my portfolio

linkedin.com/in/roncajan

- ronil.cajan@gmail.com
- +63-918-711-2668
- www.ronilcajan.com

## **Education History**

**Bachelor of Information Technology** 

Institution: University of Science and Technology of Southern Philippines -Oroqueita

Year of Graduation: 2020
• IT Governor, IT Club

- DOST Scholar
- IT Passport Level 1 Passer

### Relevant Skills

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL
- Laravel, Codelgniter, PHP
- Git, Linux, Windows, Apache